export const fetchQue = async () => {
    return [
        {
            correctAnswer: 0,
            options: [
                "Sisodia Rajput",
                "Maurya Empire",
                "Mughal Empire",
                "Gupta Dynasty",
            ],
            question: "Udaipur: Which Rajput clan founded it?Udaipur: Which Rajput clan founded it?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 2,
            options: ["Lake Pichola", "Fateh Sagar", "Lake Palace", "Lake Badi"],
            question: "Udaipur's Lake Palace: Which lake is it on?Udaipur's Lake Palace: Which lake is it on?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 1,
            options: ["1559", "1568", "1576", "1585"],
            question: "Udaipur: When did the Mughals attack?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },

        {
            correctAnswer: 0,
            options: [
                "Sisodia Rajput",
                "Maurya Empire",
                "Mughal Empire",
                "Gupta Dynasty",
            ],
            question: "Udaipur: Which Rajput clan founded it?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 2,
            options: ["Lake Pichola", "Fateh Sagar", "Lake Palace", "Lake Badi"],
            question: "Udaipur's Lake Palace: Which lake is it on?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 1,
            options: ["1559", "1568", "1576", "1585"],
            question: "Udaipur: When did the Mughals attack?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },

        {
            correctAnswer: 0,
            options: [
                "Sisodia Rajput",
                "Maurya Empire",
                "Mughal Empire",
                "Gupta Dynasty",
            ],
            question: "Udaipur: Which Rajput clan founded it?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 2,
            options: ["Lake Pichola", "Fateh Sagar", "Lake Palace", "Lake Badi"],
            question: "Udaipur's Lake Palace: Which lake is it on?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 1,
            options: ["1559", "1568", "1576", "1585"],
            question: "Udaipur: When did the Mughals attack?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },

        {
            correctAnswer: 0,
            options: [
                "Sisodia Rajput",
                "Maurya Empire",
                "Mughal Empire",
                "Gupta Dynasty",
            ],
            question: "Udaipur: Which Rajput clan founded it?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 2,
            options: ["Lake Pichola", "Fateh Sagar", "Lake Palace", "Lake Badi"],
            question: "Udaipur's Lake Palace: Which lake is it on?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 1,
            options: ["1559", "1568", "1576", "1585"],
            question: "Udaipur: When did the Mughals attack?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },

        {
            correctAnswer: 0,
            options: [
                "Sisodia Rajput",
                "Maurya Empire",
                "Mughal Empire",
                "Gupta Dynasty",
            ],
            question: "Udaipur: Which Rajput clan founded it?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 2,
            options: ["Lake Pichola", "Fateh Sagar", "Lake Palace", "Lake Badi"],
            question: "Udaipur's Lake Palace: Which lake is it on?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },
        {
            correctAnswer: 1,
            options: ["1559", "1568", "1576", "1585"],
            question: "Udaipur: When did the Mughals attack?",
            region: "Udaipur",
            timeout: 15,
        },

    ];
};
